Hell yeah. This feels sweet up here.
>> So, let's uh welcome to town. Congrats.
>> Thank you so much.
>> Let's just start. Why Detroit? Why why
did you feel like this was a fit for you
and your running style?
>> Yes. Uh it was a great opportunity uh me
and my agent sat down and talked and
you know the position we've been in uh
through the run the stretch uh it's been
on the wave but knowing the the
mentality that uh the the aggression I I
bring the uh finding who I'm going to
play for next that that could
accommodate that and coach and the staff
here the Ford family uh they they
believed in me and gave me the
opportunity to to give 110% here and I'm
going to show y'all uh that the real 10
is back.
>> You look at the combination of Sonic and
Knuckles that been successful last few
years here, man. Some people might look
at that as pressure coming in and that,
but how are you looking at it coming in
off this tandem being so successful and
you having a chance to follow up and
build your own kind of kind of kind of
kind of legacy here with with with Jir
as well?
>> Yes, definitely. Uh Jir, a hell of a
player. Um, hats off to him and the
guys, they've been putting in work here
for a couple years now. And me just
looking outside in, um, just hell of a
group. And whatever, whatever I can do
to contribute to the team, um, it's
going to happen. And whether it's
punting the ball, wherever's wherever's
at, don't matter where I'm at on the
field, cheering the guys on, um,
bringing excitement to the team and
bringing the leadership accountability.
Um, and two-time champ. Uh, not
satisfied though. Uh, that's something
that I'm not satisfied with. Um, I'm
more hungry than I ever was. Um,
and I'm ready to get to work.
>> What do you make of the the last two
seasons as you had such a strong start
to your career? Um, how much did the the
broken leg kind of sap your, you know,
calling cards and speed and power and
how much do you feel like you can get
back to the player you were before that
injury?
>> Yes, definitely. Uh, definitely was a
crazy, uh, experience going through
that. never broke a bone like to that
extreme. But it was definitely a major
comeback and just having the the mindset
of of winning a day every day coming in
the building, winning a day to get back
um to to get next to the guys. Uh
showing that I'm in the building, you
know, when you're injured, you're out of
the building. Just being around the
guys, showing them that I'm there. So
when I did step back foot on the field,
I wasn't like I was missing. Um yes, it
can slow you down, but having that
mentality of a dog and you know, un un
unsatisfied is is is important when it
comes to this cuz you could get really
comfortable with the circumstances and
for me just unsatisfied and to get back
to you with the Sonic and it and they
could call me Taz. I'm I'mma go crazy.
I'mma spin, jump, whatever I could do to
get the first down uh to cominate Jir. U
and we're fast. Uh we got speed and they
can't sleep on it.
I want to go back to the uh the Super
Bowls. Uh what how do you feel like
you're a different player? Like how did
that shape your perspective like coming
into this building now? Um just what
what are you able to to kind of share
with guys just from that experience and
how do you think that makes you a better
teammate, better leader?
>> Yes. Uh so coming in from the day one,
setting a standard. That's that's the
main thing. Coming in here and setting a
standard and accountability. Um got guys
that, you know, work different around
the building. Me, I'm going to set a
standard coming in 110%. And that's
important when you got someone that's
new coming in the building, you observe
them. Um, and as players, you you will
observe. When I was in another team and
seen players that come in, we observed
them as players. And that's who you
figure out who you're going to go to war
with. For me, uh, set the first and the
best impression. Uh, I'm hungry and I
want to win it, uh, here, not nowhere
else.
>> Are you a type of guy that is is fueled
by people doubting you? I mean,
obviously Kansas City decided to go a
different direction. You were, you know,
drafted where you were drafted. Like,
are you a guy that kind of internalizes
that and turns it into the product on
the field?
>> Yes, absolutely. I've been through
adversity my whole life. So, just
fueling adding fuel to the fire uh will
help me win the day. Um, today was today
was a roller coaster, but the staff,
everybody, they showed me around the
building. Uh I'm very blessed and
thankful to have them in my corner. Uh
it's just made it so much easier for me
today to come in here and get ready for
you guys as well. And most importantly,
just finding that that that mentality um
in in every player, that DNA um is is
the win.
>> You mentioned you mentioned Dan. Um what
have your initial conversations with him
been like and how do you feel like you
guys kind of mirror each other?
Oh man, our first conversation I was
screaming ON THE PHONE, "AH, LET'S GO.
I'M READY TO GO. PUT ME IN." He's like,
"Oh yeah, PCO. What number are you
going? Are you going with 10?" Right.
Let's go. I'M ON MY WAY. I'M coming
home.
So that was the the the whole adrenaline
during the call and I just I just
couldn't thank them enough for just, you
know, thinking of me. Um there was a lot
of teams I had I had eight opportunities
to go to different teams. Uh Kansas City
was one of them. But once they made that
move, uh I know that I had to look
forward to opening up the doors to going
somewhere else. And this was the first
place I thought of. Um my father's a
Leo. He's a lion. So we're going far,
baby.
>> Can you explain a little bit more? I
mean, we've seen it from afar, you know,
for your whole career, but that that
violent rushing style, like where does
it come from?
>> Yes. Uh that violent rushing style comes
from being unsatisfied. Going out there
on the field, you're never going to know
when your last play. Going out there
making that play for your teammate
will will show them that you care about
them and vice versa. When you got a wide
receiver blocking down the field as a
running back, you love that because when
you get the opportunity to block for
him, you're going to finish everything
and in a way to help him get positive
yardage. So that just comes with the
mentality of of being accountable to
each other. And
>> what does football mean to you?
>> Football is
is my art. Um
I love it. Um I bleed it.
I die for this. It sounds crazy, but I
love it to that much. And I wouldn't
want to be anywhere else besides here on
this day and with this new family. Um,
we got something to prove and we're
going to write the story.
>> Do you have any uh connections on this
roster? Any guys that that you know from
college or pros?
>> Yes. Uh, one of the guys today that got
was signed in today is Christian Izzian,
which is one of my former teammates from
Ruckers
>> and Kirby Joseph, Jir J
St. Brown's Golf like hit me up. That
was like like a I'm on my way here and
golf text me gave me a shot and I'm he's
like, "Hey brother, I'm glad to have you
a part of the team. I can't wait to get
to work." And I'm like right there like
bro like let's do it. Let's set the
standard uh day one. I'm excited to get
to work with you and I just can't wait
to block my ass off for him, man. And
and I know the O line is showing what
type of player I am. U it starts at
practice first. Can you maybe this ties
into what Justin asked earlier about the
injuries, but you know, you said early
on the real 10, you want to show
everybody the real 10 is back. What
happened to the real 10 the last two
years?
>> Yes. You know, through opportunities,
uh, you make the best of them. I can't
only control what I control. Um, if I'm
only getting 100 carries, I'm getting
100. If I'm getting 20, I'm getting 20.
I control what I control. Uh, keep the
same mentality every day in the
building. Go in there smiling. uh get
guys going and make sure the team we're
were heading in the right direction as a
leader being on time to those uh
leadership council meetings either if I
was the start or not starting or it
didn't matter if I was if my name was on
that board I was in there in that
meeting on time and wherever I had to be
set the standard in the room uh for the
for the younger guys.
>> You mentioned, you know, the success you
obviously enjoyed in Kansas City. Uh
this team's been close for a couple
years. How close do you think this team
is to maybe enjoying some of that and
how much a part of your decision was
that?
>> Yes. So watching from afar um very close
and just being a player and a teammate
um not a father but one day and just
being someone that they could look
forward to and count on and look to the
left and right and know that he got my
back. And that's the type of player I
am. And for everybody in the building,
um we're going to win together. That's
what it's all about together. Doing
everything together.
>> You did face this team a couple times in
Casey. What was your impression, I
guess, of of them?
>> Oh, the impression of them. They had
some big boys on that line. Damn. Every
time I seen old line, I'm like I'm just
sitting back like
they're all like 7 foot. I'm like, damn,
who the hell? Who their dads? So, I'm
like, as a younger guy, you know, you
get to you get to be around, you know,
some special guys. And everybody has a
different u different mentalities and
you know for me as a as a younger guy
that's still growing and willing to
learn um just mindful of I'm all ears
open and I'm willing to learn. What do
>> you feel like a new start a new
beginning just like just new new new
situation can do for you? Do you feel
rejuvenated in a sense at all?
>> Absolutely. um felt won it and now is
the time or was the time to, you know,
to to build off of the previous years.
You going to have doubters, it comes
with it. Um it's how you uh it's how you
perform and how you react and I know
that I'm willing to to give it all 110%
and it's what I love to do.
>> You look back on your time in in KC, you
know, obviously had a lot of success
there. I don't know how it ended, but
you know, just how do you how do you
sort of look back in the last four
years?
>> I love every single one of those coaches
in the building, players, uh EQ, it goes
down the line. Like, everyone treated me
like like you want to get treated in in
a building. And that's what brotherhood
was about. and just coming from that,
reflecting on them and just bringing
something to my life as a player, uh
maybe a father one day and just knowing
that whatever you do, do it do it all
100%. Um you got guys, you build friends
off of the leadership. Um you know what
I mean? When you're accountable, you can
bring the whole team with you and that's
what it takes um to bring the whole
team.
Just curious, you brought up the the
blocking for for Jared. We we see some
of the numbers there. It looks, you
know, like you're pretty strong in that
department. You know, where does that
mindset come from? Was that something
you came from college with or is that
something that came and was developed at
the pros?
>> Yes, it's something I came from college
with. Um coming from high school playing
quarterback, going into college playing
running back, that was the most
important part of my game I had to build
at was blocking, blocking, blocking
because you quarterback, you're dropping
back all day long. you're not you're not
making blocks. And that was the main
goal, figuring out a way to get down
there, put my chin in and the guy under
his chin strap and and hold him up. And
as the years go, getting better and
better every camp, uh this where you let
the dog out and that's where you get
after each other. You make you sharp
iron sharpen iron in camp and that's
where you that's where the magic
happens.
>> Quarterback were you?
>> Last one.
>> Running. I mean, what you know,
>> I was a running throwing quarterback. Uh
I I rushed for,00 yards this quarter.
That's why I was a lot of running.
A lot of running. Uh 500 passing yards.
Not that much, but
still that at that point playing that.
>> Yes. My high school coach Russo always
told me, "Hey 10." Well, I was in 10 at
the time. I was number one. A one, be
smart. Run out of bounds. You don't need
to take those extra hits. Cuz I was
always like just wanted to crush
somebody. Just wanted to crush them. But
as the years go on, you got to get
smarter about it.